试镜如何
Oh, hey! How was your audition?
抱歉  我认识你吗
I'm sorry, do I know you?
你这是要干嘛
What are you doing?
练习假装不认识你  我要成为电影明星了
I'm just practicing blowing you off. I'm gonna be a big movie star!
你拿到那个角色了
You got it?
还没  但试镜很成功
No, not yet, but the audition went really good!
什么样的角色
What's it for?
大成本制作  关于三个意大利兄弟...
It's a big-budget period movie about three Italian brothers...
在世纪之初来到美国
...who come to America at the turn of the century.
是个经典故事
It's really classy.
本片导演被认为会成为下下个马丁·史柯西斯
The director's supposed to be the next-next Martin Scorsese.
"下下个"
The "next-next"?
芝加哥的那个家伙被认为是下个马丁·史柯西斯
A guy from Chicago's supposed to be the next Martin Scorsese.
这个导演紧排在他之后
This guy's right after him.
喂
Hello?
乔伊  我是艾丝特尔
Joey, it's Estelle.
我刚和选角人员谈过  他们很喜欢你
I just talked to the casting people. They loved you!
他们很喜欢我
They loved me!
他们明天要再见你一次
Yeah, they want to see you again tomorrow.
-我的天啊  -只有一个问题
- My God! - There's just one thing.
你对正面全裸有问题吗
Do you have a problem with full-frontal nudity?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding me?
我租的电影部部都有正面全裸镜头
I never rent a movie without it!
好  我再回你电话
Okay, let me call you back.
怎么回事
What's the matter?
电影需要我全裸出镜
They want me naked in the movie.
-天啊  -是啊
- Wow! - I know.
我祖母会看到的
My grandmother's gonna see this.
祖母想看还得排队呢
Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
婚礼就快到了  你紧张吗
The wedding's so close. Are you getting nervous?
我都等不及赶紧结束了
Yeah, but a part of me also can't wait till it's over.
我们决定婚礼前禁欲
Chandler and I have a pact not to have sex again until the wedding.
"无性"条约
A "no sex" pact, huh?
我和全美每位女性都签了这份合约
I actually have one of those with every woman in America.
菲比  你能帮我整理客房吗
Phoebe, will you give me a hand making up the guest bedroom?
凯西要来和我们住几天
Cousin Cassie's staying with us for a few days.
凯西  我很久没见过她了
Cassie? I haven't seen her in, like, forever.
她是不是还带着芭比娃娃到处跑
I wonder if she still carries that Barbie everywhere she goes?
-她都25岁了  -所以呢  我还...
- Ross, she's 25 years old. - So what? I still...
对  你说得没错
No, you're probably right.
菲比  我可以和你说句话吗
Pheebs, can I talk to you over here for a second?
好
Yeah.
要低调一点
Subtle, guys.
怎么了
What?
我知道你们在为我策划单身女郎惊喜派对
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
好吧  别破坏了惊喜
Okay, well, don't ruin it.
至少假装不知道
Just play along, at least.
好  对不起
Okay. Sorry.
天啊  我们还要替她办单身女郎派对
Oh, my god. We have to throw her a shower?
你决定接不接那部电影了吗
What'd you decide to do about the movie?
我不知道  我是说...
I don't know. I mean...
这不是部色情电影
It's not like it's porn.
这是一部严肃  正当的电影
This is a serious, legitimate movie.
这个故事里的裸戏很重要
Nudity's really important to the story.
你对色情电影也是这种看法
That's what you say about porn.
我大概不该去参加复试
Maybe I shouldn't go on the callback.
不  你应该去  很多大明星都有裸戏演出
No, you should. A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
这可是个当电影主演的机会  别随便放弃
The chance to star in a movie? Come on!
说得对  而且我只有一场裸戏
That's true. And I'm only naked in one scene.
听着真的很不错
It sounds really great.
我的角色是个天主教徒
My character's Catholic.
他和一位犹太女孩相恋了
He falls in love with a Jewish girl.
我们为爱私奔而被困在大雨中
We run away and get caught in a big rainstorm.
躲到谷仓里  脱掉彼此的衣服抱在一起
We go into a barn, undress each other and hold each other.
真的是甜密而温柔
It's really sweet and tender.
还有  每个人都看到你那话儿
Plus, everyone will see your thing!
我们可以何时举办单身女郎派对
When can we have this shower?
她的日程排得那么满  我们只有两个选择
She has so much going on, we have only two options.
-可以定在星期五  -只剩两天了
- We have Friday. - That's just two days away.
-还可以选在哪天  -昨天
- What is the other option? - Yesterday.
如果我们安排在昨天  事情就搞定了
If we make it yesterday, we're done!
菲比  不可能  我们不可能定在星期五
My god, Phoebe, it's impossible. We can't do this by Friday.
要找场地  邀请客人  置办食物
We have to find a place. We have to invite people! We have to get food!
有太多要做了  根本不可能
There's just too much to do! It's impossible!
-办不到  根本办不到  -镇静下来
- We can't do it! We cannot do it! We cannot do it! - Calm down!
好  抱歉  你说得对  抱歉
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. I'm sorry.
镇静下来  姑娘
Just calm down, woman!
菲比  我已经镇静下来了
Phoebe, I already did.
好吧  那是我需要镇静
All right, then I need to calm down.
只要我们把思路理顺  还是能办到的
I think we can do this if we just get organized.
我们有两天来计划这个聚会
We have two days to plan this party.
做决定要快
We just need to make fast decisions.
好  要在哪里办
Okay, where will we have it?
-在这里  几点  -四点  食物
- Here. What time? - 4:00. Food?
-小三明治和茶  -好极了  很莫妮卡
- Finger sandwiches and tea. - Great! Very Monica.
-还有辣椒  -太过头了
- And chili! - You went one too far.
-花还是气球  -两个都要
- Flowers or balloons? - Both.
-要我们自己买单  -两个都不要
- We're paying for this. - Neither.
主题定什么呢
What should we do for a theme?
肌肤之欲
Lusts of the Flesh!
-什么  -要不就牛仔风
- What? - I don't know. Cowboy theme?
很高兴我们决定婚礼前不上床
I'm really glad we decided not to sleep together before the wedding.
我也是
Oh, boy. Me too.
我在想  如果我们大吵一架
I was thinking, say we had a big fight,
-分手几个小时  -是
- and we broke up for a few hours. - Yeah.
严格来说  我们就可以上床了
Technically, we could have sex again.
你说呢  颐指气使的婆娘
What do you think, bossy and domineering?
婚礼取消了  长不大的邋遢鬼
The wedding's off, sloppy and immature.
说的正是我  走吧
That's me. Come on.
等一下  凯西在客房
Wait. My cousin Cassie's in the guest room.
我们要出去吃午饭
We're supposed to have lunch.
甩掉她  有强迫症的高嗓门
Get rid of her, obsessive and shrill!
高嗓门  婚礼照常
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
我听到有人在讲话  你一定就是钱德勒
I thought I heard voices. You must be Chandler.
-很高兴认识你  -很高兴认识你
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you too.
-可以走了吗  -可以了
- So, ready to go? - Yeah.
-钱德勒  -我马上就来
- Chandler? - I'll be right with you.
-凯西必须住到你家  -为什么
- Cassie needs to stay at your place. - Why?
因为这位"变态"一直瞪着她看
Because "Pervie Perverson" over here can't stop staring at her.
钱德勒  她可是我们的表妹
What? Chandler, she's our cousin!
我没有瞪着她看  我是很专心地听她说话
I wasn't staring at her. I was just listening intently.
做一位好的倾听者  看着
It's called being a good conversationalist. Watch.
说话
Say something.
你刚才盯着南边八英尺外的地方
You were staring about eight inches south of there.
好  她可以住我家
Fine. She can stay at my place.
凯西现在长什么样子
By the way, what does Cassie even look like now?
跟玛丽莲姨妈一模一样
She looks exactly like Aunt Marilyn.
玛丽莲姨妈会来参加婚礼吗
This Aunt Marilyn, is she coming to the wedding?
你给我小心点
Wafer-thin ice.
我回来了
Hey, I'm back.
乔伊
Hi, Joey.
我要念同一场戏吗
Will I read the same scene again?
我打过电话给你  你今天不用过来的
Actually, I tried to call you. You didn't need to come down here today.
真好
Oh, great.
我是这个角色的最佳人选
You know I'd have been perfect for this part, but whatever.
你这个错误决定会毁了整部电影  再见
Thanks for making a bad decision and ruining your movie! Good day!
乔伊  你不需要过来
Joey, you didn't need to come down,
因为导演看了你的带子非常喜欢
because the director saw your tape from yesterday and loved it.
还有表演
And, scene.
很好玩吧  刚刚的即兴表演
Wasn't that fun? We did a little improv there. Yeah!
你刚才想说什么
So, you were saying?
导演觉得你很适合这个角色
The director thinks you're really right for the part
明天想见你
and wants to meet you tomorrow.
当然  太好了
Wow! Sure! That's great.
你经纪人说你对裸戏没问题
Your agent said you're okay with nudity.
是  只要表现得有格调一些
Yeah, sure. As long as it's handled tastefully.
谷仓不要太冷就行
And that barn is not too cold.
好极了  还有一件事
Perfect. There's one more thing.
导演希望电影里
It's important to the director
每一处细节都还原现实
that everything in the movie's authentic.
你和莎拉的性爱场面...
So in your love scene with Sarah...
她说自己从没见过非犹太的裸体男子
...she talks about how she's never seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
所以...
So...
所以...怎么样
So... what?
导演坚持出演这个角色的人...
So, the director is insisting that whoever play that part...
是正宗的  在人体结构上...
...be authentically, anatomically...
不是犹太人  你知道我的意思吗
...not Jewish. You know what I'm saying?
知道
Yes!
不知道  什么意思
No. What?
那时意大利天主教移民没有...
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would not be...
行过受诚礼
Bar mitzvah-ed?
-想拿到这个角色  你不能...  -对
- To get this part, you can't be... - No.
-可你是  -对
- But you are? - Yeah.
-但你告诉他们你不是  -对
- But you told them you weren't? - That's right.
真的完全没有了吗
It's definitely all gone?
一点努力的余地都没有吗
There's nothing there to work with?
你当时是怎么想的
What were you thinking?
我不知道  我超想拿到这个角色
I don't know. I really want this part.
他们说不管试镜时被问到什么问题
They tell you no matter what you're asked during an audition,
都回答是
you say yes.
如果要求你骑马  就说你会
Like if they want you to ride a horse, tell them you can.
之后再想办法解决
And you just figure out how to do it later.
这和学骑马可不一样
Joey, this is not like learning to ride a horse.
这就像是要学会...
This is like learning...
长出一件高领毛衣
...to grow a turtleneck.
我知道
I know, I know, okay?
明天我去见导演的时候
Apparently, tomorrow, when I go meet the director...
我必须脱光衣服
I have to take my clothes off
让他们看到我身体的全貌
so they can see what my body looks like.
你要怎么办啊
What are you gonna do?
我得打给经纪人告诉她我不能接这个角色了
I have to call my agent and tell her I can't do the part.
除非...
Unless...
除非什么
Unless what?
虽说听着疯狂  但我们可能可以做点...
This may sound crazy, but there may be something we could...
造型
...fashion.
-比如呢  -我还没思路
- Like what? - Well, I'm not sure yet, but...
不过我的第一反应是
Off the top of my head, I'm thinking...
双面胶带加某种午餐肉
...double-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
我有个关于派对主题的好主意
I've got a great idea for party favors for the shower.
找一些红木盒子  刻上每个人的名字
Okay, we get mahogany boxes and carve everyone's names in them.
在里面放上每个人的出生石
Then inside is each persors individual birthstone.
好  好
Okay. Okay.
你来搞定
You take care of that.
派对就在明天  我们还没有宾客名单
And meanwhile, the party's tomorrow and we don't have a guest list.
好吧  我们知道要来的有谁
Okay. Who do we know that's coming?
有我  你要来吗
Me. Are you?
怎么样啊  莫妮卡
Hey, what's up, Mon?
我在替乔伊做东西  可以搜一下你的冰箱吗
I'm making something for Joey. Do you mind I raid your fridge?
请便
Have at it.
好  火鸡肉  没有用
All right. Turkey? That won't work.
奶酪  没有用
Cheese? That won't work.
橄榄面包  希望没用
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
你在替他做三明治吗
Are you making him a sandwich?
不  比较像是鸡肉卷
No, it's more like a wrap.
好  我要走了
Okay, so I'm gonna go, guys.
你们可以继续讨论要送我什么礼物
So you can get back to deciding on what to get me for a present!
我们还要送她礼物
We have to get her a present?
好吧  看我拿到了什么
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
她的通讯录  我们的宾客名单
It's her address book. We have a guest list.
你好厉害  你从她皮包拿的吗
Oh, my god. You're amazing. Did you pull that out of her purse?
还有办派对的启动资金
Uh-huh. And a little seed money for the party.
凯西
Cassie?
罗斯
Hey, Ross!
好久不见
It's been so long!
上一次我见到你时
Last time I saw you...
你还搭着帐篷排队买《绝地归来》的电影票
...you were setting up your tent in line for Return of the Jedi.
对
That's right.
所以那天你有看到我了  却装作没看到
So you did see me that day. Because it seemed like you didn't.
-对不起  -没关系  请进
- Yeah, sorry about that. - It's okay. Come on in.
谢谢你让我住在这儿  莫妮卡家不错
Thanks for letting me stay here. Monica's place was nice.
但她未婚夫一直瞪着我看
But her fiance sure stares a lot.
天啊  你学钱德勒学得真像
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
我有模仿才能
I have a knack for impressions.
等我们再熟一点  你也可以学[干]我
Maybe after we get re-acquainted you could do me.
好  不要
Yeah. No!
凯西  你的...
Cassie, how you doing on that...
热狗吃得怎样了
...hot dog?
-我吃完了  -感谢上帝
- I'm all done. - Thank God.
我们上次一起出去玩
I guess the last time we hung out was
是那次我们父母一起租了那座沙滩别墅
when our parents rented that beach house together.
记得我当时骑在你身上
Remember the time I pinned you down
把你胳肢哭了
and tickled you until you cried?
我们现在大了  不能那么闹了
We're probably too old to do that now.
我一直都记得那个夏天
I'll always remember that summer.
我就是那时长了这些雀斑
Because it's when I got all these freckles.
我一直都记得那个夏天...
I'll always remember that summer...
因为那时我才意识到我们是亲戚
...because that's when I realized that we are related.
你花了那么久才发现
It took you that long to figure it out?
我是有点反应迟钝
I'm a little slow.
我们的孩子也会这样
Just as our children would be.
你好吗  好  谢谢大家能来
How are you? Good. Hi. Thanks for coming.
谢谢  很高兴见到你
Thank you. So nice to see you.
-不用  谢谢  -好  瑞秋
- No, thanks. - Okay. Hey, Rach?
-怎么了  -这些都是什么人啊
- Yeah? - Who the hell are all these people?
不知道  我给电话簿里的所有人都打了电话
I don't know. I called everybody in Monica's phone book.
这些是在24小时内通知还能赶过来的
These are the ones that could show up on 24 hours' notice.
有另一个词来形容这种人  废柴
There's a another word for people like that: Losers.
我是瑞秋  这是菲比  我是伴娘
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe. I'm the maid of honor.
你怎么认识莫妮卡的
How do you know Monica?
我是她四年前的会计师
I was her accountant four years ago.
我很想知道
I'm very interested to find out
这过去四年是谁替她报税
who's been doing her taxes the last four years.
很好
That's great.
-莫妮卡何时会到  -我不知道
- When is Monica supposed to get here? - I don't know.
借一步说话
Excuse us.
-你没告诉她吗  -你该通知她的
- You didn't tell her to come? - You were supposed to tell her.
不是我
No, I wasn't.
是你负责通知她
You were supposed to tell her to come!
我负责带蛋糕
And I was supposed to bring the cake!
好  我打电话给她
Fine, I'll go call her.
快去  顺便要她带蛋糕来
Yes, and please tell her to bring a cake!
我们有多种选择
Okay, we have a lot of options here.
有好几种"鸡"型可以试戴
A number of prototypes for you to try on.
-看起来很棒  -是啊
- Those look great. -Yeah.
这是磨菇帽  这是意大利香肠做的
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap. This one is made of bologna.
-牙签  -只是撑着等胶水干掉
- The toothpicks? - Just until the glue dries.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
这些比较逼真  但会腐烂
These are more realistic, but perishable.
这边  粉红色的山羊皮  很不错
Over here, we have pink suede, which is nice.
但湿了会缩水
But if it gets wet, it'll shrink.
那就不要了
Maybe we'll just take that one away.
我还用皮毛做了个小玩意
I also did a little something in fur,
不过是留给我自己的
but that's really just for me.
不如你去试试这些
Why don't you go into your room and try these on?
我们就知道哪些效果好了
We'll get a better idea of what's gonna work.
谢谢  你真是位好朋友  这感觉太诡异了
Thanks, you are such a good friend. And this is so weird.
-被牙签扎到  -对
- Toothpick? - Yeah.
-你现在在试哪个  -水果卷
- What are you trying now? - The Fruit Roll-up.
-然后呢  -很好吃
- And? - Delicious.
乔伊
Joey!
等一下  等一下  冠军出线了
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We have a winner!
怎么样  哪一个
What? Which one?
橡皮泥  质量很坚挺哦
The Silly Putty. Not so silly anymore!
她是你表妹  她是你表妹
She's your cousin. She's your cousin.
如果她知道你脑袋里在想什么
If she knew what was going on in your head,
她会以为你是变态
she'd think you were sick.
她会那么以为吗  回想一下
Or would she? Let's back up for a second.
是她提议开的红酒
She was the one who suggested opening a bottle of wine.
是她把灯光调暗的
She was the one who turned down the lights.
是她要租《二十三世纪大逃亡》的...
She was the one that wanted to rent Logars Run...
这可是有史以来最性感的电影
...the sexiest movie ever.
我知道这种眼神
I know that look.
不管了  我想要  她也想要
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
我要行动了
I'm going in.
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
说点漂亮话
Say something clever.
好吧  不必是漂亮话
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
随便说点什么  说话
Just has to be words. Say some words.
什么话都行
Any words will do.
天啊  这是有史以来...
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
最长的沉默
...that anyone has not talked ever!
说什么都不可能比现在更尴尬了
There is nothing you could say to make this worse...
说点什么
...so just say something!
我很久没做爱了
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
你还不如保持沉默
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
菲比  瑞秋  是莫妮卡
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
什么事这么急着找我来呢
I wonder what you could possibly need me for on such short notice?
-莫妮卡  我们很抱歉  -怎么了
- Oh, Monica. We are so sorry. - For what?
先是忘了替你办单身女郎派对
First, for forgetting to throw you a bridal shower.
然后又忘了邀请你
Then, forgetting to invite you to it.
你们已经办完了
You already had it?
我们给你通讯录里的每一个人打了电话
We called everyone in your phone book.
来了很多人
A bunch of people came.
但把你找来花了太长时间  客人都走了
It took us so long to get you here that they had to leave.
我们想给你一个大惊喜
We wanted to throw you a big surprise
替你办一场精彩的单身女郎派对
and a great shower.
现在两样都泡汤了
Now you don't have either.
我们把一切都搞砸了
We ruined everything.
等一下  没有搞砸啊
No, wait a minute, that's not true.
你们真的很贴心
What you did was really sweet.
-其实这样子最好  -什么意思
- It kind of works out for the best. - What do you mean?
现在我可以和真正喜欢的人一起
Now I get to spend my shower
共渡我的单身女郎派对
with the only people I really love.
我不仅有礼物收
I get all those presents
还不必和我不喜欢的人说话
without talking to people I don't even like!
-惊喜  -惊喜  莫妮卡
- Surprise. - Surprise, Monica.
最酷的是  这个角色是从尼泊尔来的
What's cool is, the character is from Naples, right?
我全家都是从尼泊尔来的
My whole family's from Naples.
太好了  情况我了解得差不多了
That's great. Okay. I've heard everything I need to hear...
我们只需要...
We just need to, uh...
莱斯莉
Leslie?
-乔伊  这个环节有点尴尬  -没有问题
- Joey, this is the awkward part. - Hey, right. Not a problem.
我完全了解...
I totally understand you need...
你们需要确定我没有严重的疤痕或纹身
...to make sure I don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
不用担心
Don't you worry.
我没什么可隐藏的
I have nothing to hide.
好了  这就是我
So, there you go. That's me.
百分之百纯天然
One hundred percent natural.
这种事从来没发生过
I tell you, that has never happened before.
凯西  一切都还好吗
Cassie, are you finding everything okay in there?
是  谢谢你让我住在这儿
Yeah. Thank you so much for letting me stay here.
客气什么
Oh, it's no problem.
怎么
What?
说话  随便说什么
Say something. Say anything.
约她出去  她又不是你表妹
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!